He's currently in a deep REM
sleep and has been for some time.
He woke up in a posture
like an ascetic monk
and when it seemed like he might be awake.
He went back to sleep for 24 hours.
Makes sense since he has
zero memory to speak of.
How are his learning and cognitive
skills after being revived?
They're all normal.
He's even memorized 30 english words.
However he doesn't seem to
know or understand his name.
is Jotaro Kujo.
As for his family, he shows no reaction,
not even to a picture of his daughter.
His EEG and EKG read is normal too.
However, his muscle
values are on the decline.
Having no memories would
indicate that he naturally has
no motivation to go on living
as the mind is shutting down.
In response, the muscles
begin to deteriorate quickly.
All right, Doctor.
What's the plan?
I don't know yet.
We may have no other choice here than
to try and get his memories back.
Doctor, wait!
Don't touch his head!
He's injured!
Get him some first aid!
I apologize, Doctor.
I forgot to warn you about that before.
Did he just release his stand power? Yes.
However, it's actually not from his
memory, but rather an instinctive defense.
It says Jolene.
Wait, Jolene?
No, no way.
It couldn't possibly say.
I want you to know.
You were always incredibly
important to me.
Holy shit.
Look at the wounds on your arm.
Even though I treated them.
Even though I healed them.
They've formed shapes
that spell something out.
Clearly.
I'll try healing them again.
No, wait.
I don't want you to heal this.
I have no way to explain it.
But I know this is a
message sent from my dad
since before I was even born.
That man has been watching over so many
things to keep mama and I from being
involved in scenarios exactly like
the ones that are going on right now.
He made sure to keep his
distance, knowing that
it helped me stay safe.
Yes, just now.
I felt it.
I believe that through my
body, my dad speaks to me.
Thank you so much for watching.
I am because of me
Break out!
We are coming from you We can't do
this since we have a chance Break out!
We can't do this whole way.
It is a lot of the wrong.
We must love to change.
I will not stop waiting!
Don't stop waiting?
Don't stop beating a man!
Not what you think I won't
actually allow her to fall down you
see as soon as she stumbles I'm
going to catch her in my arms huh
the thing is she might not understand
that she was protected earlier
because of me what I desire is
to feel her in my embrace again
so go do it now come on just trip
harassment and assault that's
on your buddy I'll tell you again
I'm going to make Jolene my wife
and you are going to help me with
that are you the sort of person
who breaks their promises now do
it I'm sorry Jolene but I have to
I caught the small man
he must have been spying
on us from the floor
above the The whole time!
That's it!
He's holding the bone
in his hand right there!
Well, he sure is a slippery
little fucker, isn't he?
But he won't escape me!
No, wait.
Something's wrong with his back.
You said earlier that he
was a small man, right?
He indeed fit that category before.
But now, he's somehow...
Sunbathing.
...getting much taller before our eyes.
As tall as me.
No, even taller, in fact.
Hey, you're cornered.
No more running away.
Now face me nice and slow.
Feels good.
The sun.
The light.
Hey, I'm talking to you,
asshole! Look at me!
Uh...
What's wrong with this guy?!
Light is...
Warm.
It's very lively.
Everyone gathers here, and it's so warm.
Uh...
What the hell?
His head literally just exploded!
Do you think he's a stand user?
Just stay away.
No, it doesn't look like a stand.
I don't know what it is, but whatever
we do, we shouldn't touch him.
Shit, where'd the bone go?
He was holding it earlier.
What happened?
We have to find it.
Holy crap!
It's happening to the other inmates, too?
They're undeniably turning into plants.
They appear to still be
growing, too. But why?
What's happening to them all?
Who could have done this?
What possible reason could anyone have?
Perhaps I should think of
this as a stand power as well.
of the bone.
It seems like the power and will fueling
this phenomenon is in so doing attempting
to give life to something entirely new.
Flowers bloomed, as well as stems
leaves even a tiny little trunk.
And at the end of that, well then, what
should I do with the bone that the small
man dropped?
This is a conundrum.
I now know that it's
dangerous to touch the bone,
to say nothing Of
touching anyone else who's
come into contact with it
stop right there Jolene
Kujo don't go Any further
I told you to stop turn
around and look at me I
want to see your face now
Okay that's good just stay
there I need to check something
Hey!
Are you out of your mind?
Get away from me!
Anastasia, you pervert!
Be quiet, FF.
I'm doing this for a reason.
All the prisoners at this discipline
ward became like this, due to the bone.
It's not an enemy stand.
The enemy would have used their power
to attack us first if that were true.
Also, Jolene,
I thought that a bit earlier, With
your thread looking the way it did,
that you would touch the
bone, am I right about that?
The bone! It's rolling away!
Shit!
You've been infected, Jolene!
The hell no!
Diver, drive!
Nice one!
Anastasia, hurry it up!
Kick it all out from inside!
Wait, you're not finished yet!
It's still growing!
It's not correct or proper to say
yank it out or it's growing, FF.
The body is actually being
transformed into this.
I may not be able to simply rip these off.
Jolene, any pain?
No, but this is still bad news,
because it means I touched that bone.
What's more, since I'm turning floral,
you'd better stay far away from me.
You might get infected also.
This is simply a plant.
There's nothing more to it than that.
I don't know what kind it is,
but I do know that instead of blood running
through your veins, there's chlorophyll.
Just know, I'm going to do
something about it, without fail.
It's sunlight!
You have to stay in the shade.
If you go towards or in the
sunlight, it grows fast.
But if you move back into the
shade, the growth calms down.
Stay right where you are.
I don't get it!
What is this thing's purpose, anyway?
I have no idea, but I've
got to get that bone.
It's the only thing that matters now.
And how are you going to do that?
You touch it again, and you'll
turn into a frickin' tree.
Forget it!
No, I'm picking it up.
Because I already am one.
Stop, Jolene.
I said to stay out of the sunlight.
Get back!
The bone. Where'd it go?
Where is it?
If I'm right, it should have rolled over
here and ended up by this flower by now.
Wait, is that a star?
And what is this bruise-like thing?
I can see something showing
through from behind it, too.
Oh my god, it's a child!
A green child!
What does it look like?
Carrots that are shaped like
Snoopy and radishes that
look like big tits get harvested
from farms all the time
This must be like that, too.
I Mean it definitely looks that way.
It's alive.
No more Jolene don't even think about
touching that thing get back here now!
Haven't you noticed?
The roots are wrapping around
your leg and meshing with it.
I need to know.
Is this a plant or is it a human?
It turned the whole Discipline
Ward into a greenhouse,
connected them by its roots, then bloomed.
This weird little fruit baby probably
absorbed the bone when it was germinating.
And Palesnake is here somewhere inside
this prison to find out what's behind this.
What will come out of this pod?
He's here because he wants to know what
begins when when it's finally born.
I said get back here, Jolene!
The sun is setting in the west, so the
light's getting stronger and hotter.
If you don't step back,
it's going to get bad.
Seriously?
You're picking that up?
No, FF.
I would say it's more like stealing.
I won't let Pale Snake get
his filthy hands on it.
Let's go, Jolene.
The sooner we get you away
from sunlight, the better.
Anastasia!
Ah, hang on, this building's
exit is west-facing!
I don't know how we're gonna
get out of this shithole.
There's at least one more
enemy sand user here somewhere,
which means we're still in big-ass danger!
How to escape?
Huh.
Please!
You gotta help me!
Come on, help me!
I'm freaking out!
I'm begging you!
After everyone drowned, they
turned into grass and died!
It was terrifying!
Please help me!
I bought it turned into grass too!
Get me out of here! Fine, okay.
First, tell me your name,
and are you hurt at all?
What the fuck, Anastasia?
You realize he could be an enemy!
Well, is that true?
Are you an enemy and not telling us?
I have no idea what you're talking about!
My name is Guccio!
I... I...
I just don't want to become grass, okay?
Calm down, will you?
I already said it's fine.
Stand up, Keicho.
You can at least do that, can't you?
Come on, stand up.
Were you aware?
Humans have 12 pairs of ribs, 24 in total.
Regardless of people's
gender, weight, or height.
It's the same for everyone.
All right, you're free to go.
What was that?
So is that guy an enemy or isn't he?
Frankly, that's of no
importance to me at all.
The only thing I'm interested
in now is if we can safely
get out of here from the
east side of the building.
Are we agreed?
We should want safety.
We should make that our exit point.
I didn't expect the green child.
How did it ever come to this?
I had only the barest of information.
I have one job and it's simple:
get rid of Jolene Kujo permanently.
That's all I'm here for.
I just have to make sure I do that.
Damn it.
Where did Jolene and
those other two fools go?
Did they possibly manage to
escape and I missed them?
No.
There's no way they could get
outside without my seeing them.
Hey, you.
What are you doing there?
Hey, I asked you a question.
Where are the other three?
And why haven't you
turned into a plant yet?
I'm in agony!
They modified a human
body into a death trap!
It hurts!
I've never felt such pain!
This is horrible!
I want my mama!
My left arm is useless now!
That was an awful experience.
Tailed Snake told me to make
them fight using Survivor,
and I'm pretty sure I did that,
but what really matters now is yay,
finally, I could go
outside and be in the sun.
That was close, but it looks like we made
a clean getaway from the other stand user.
Look, it's withering.
I guess it was a temporary thing anyway.
The bigger problem to worry
about is that at any minute,
prison staffers are going to realize
what happened at this discipline ward.
That's better for us, because if they do,
Palesnake will realize
that at the same time.
And he'll come out and show his ugly face.
Which then gives me the best chance
to take my dad's memory disc back.
Cholene, look!
Stone Ocean!
It's an enemy stand!
It's probably the one that
belongs to that guy playing army!
He took the fruit!
I won't let him have it!
Tiger, drive!
What's going on?
This body...
My god, ew, the stench of him...
It's inside!
I'm trying, but I can't get in there.
I've gotten close enough
to feel the stand itself.
Wait, that repulsive
odor is coming from me.
Oh, your shoes.
Are they that dirty because of what I did?
My, I'm embarrassed.
How could I?
Here, please have a seat on this chair.
I'll let your shoes clean for you.
While you're waiting,
would you like to read the manga
I swiped from the guards' room?
Be careful, there's a bee.
Let me tell you about my master.
First off, his name is D and G.
The last I saw him, he was
in the discipline ward.
His left arm was a bleeding mess, and
he was bawling like a helpless baby.
I am Long Range Control Stand!
It's plenty to take the fruit
and run back to its master!
I noticed.
I'll be out here in a minute.
Jolene, we have to get
out of here right now.
Let's go to the marshland.
There might be a boat or at
least a water scooter there
Here's how to differentiate
wild strawberries.
The yellow one is only a mock
strawberry So you really can't eat it.
Do you ever shut the
fuck up? Wait a second.
We can't leave that stand where it is.
He swallowed the green plant, baby And
we have to get it out of him like now.
Right, I know
FF, tell that weirdo we
have to take him with us.
You have to go find the main body.
And when you do, blow him off the map.
It's my pleasure.
So I should go along with you?
Is that right, Master? Goody.
This is the exclusive
Marshland boat, Master.
You're going to love it.
It has a special propeller
powered by the wind to sail it.
You might be surprised how fast it goes.
Damn.
What about the engine?
How do I start it?
Is it locked on this boat somewhere?
It's the throttle lever, Master.
Here, let me show you.
If you want to get it in gear, you must
shift it in neutral first, like so.
The stick is the rudder.
Push it forward, the empanage,
or tail assembly turns right.
Pull it back, it turns to the left.
Simple as that. Ready?
Yes, untie the anchor rope, weirdo.
Yes, right away, Master.
Jolene, don't you dare take
your eyes off that stand.
As long as you've got him under your
watch, he'll be an excellent servant.
Perfect, even.
He's creepy, but he'll be useful.
However, if you give him any leeway...
This son of a bitch!
This is way worse than I imagined!
Jolene...
Anastasia...
Don't take your eyes off
this monster for a second!
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place
Other than he
Although you think I smile
inside and all the while,
I'm wondering
about my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.